<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="#990000"
    android:orientation="vertical"
    tools:context=".introduction">
    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent">

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:layout_marginLeft="10dp"
            android:layout_marginRight="10dp"
            android:background="#ffffff"
            android:orientation="vertical">

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginTop="15dp"
                android:text="kachi ogbonna"
                android:textAlignment="center"
                android:textAllCaps="true"
                android:textColor="#000000"
                android:textSize="30sp"
                android:textStyle="bold" />
            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginTop="12dp"
                android:text="CHALLENGES FACED"
                android:textAlignment="center"
                android:textAllCaps="true"
                android:textColor="#000000"
                android:textSize="25sp"
                android:textStyle="bold" />
            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginTop="5dp"
                android:fontFamily="sans-serif"
                android:paddingLeft="8dp"
                android:paddingRight="8dp"
                android:text="As a student entrepreneur the biggest challenge I faced was lack of a mentor to provide direction. I made so many costly mistakes that could have been avoided if I had access to a mentor. This is the reason I run HTS Mentorship Club today and I am particularly passionate about helping students entrepreneurs to avoid every mistake I made.
HOW IT HAS BEEN - THE JOURNEY SO FAR
Due to my lack of experience I couldn't sustain the businesses I started in school. So during my NYSC I started searching for new opportunities to start all over, after few months of hustling it out in the streets of Lagos and battling with traffic on my 9 to 5 job I told myself that it was time to focus on the thing that gives me joy - educating young people on the way out of the unemployment crisis in the country. I started organising entrepreneurship summit across the country, but along the line I discovered that a lot of people don't believe one can successfully build a business in a difficult environment like Nigeria. So I set out to find out how some of the innovative brands in Nigeria started, I wanted to find out how those build who built successful businesses in Nigeria did it. Unfortunately I couldn't find any book on that so I decided to write one. This is one thing I have always challenged young people about in Nigeria, if you can't find the solution to the problems around you, rather than complain, go ahead and be that solution you desire.
So, I decided to embark on a research to find out How Dangote, Globacom,  Coscharis, InterSwitch, Zinox, Jumia and other Nigerian brands started.

Though it was difficult to get across to the founders of these brands, but with persistence I was able to pull through.

That book titled HOW THEY STARTED ended up being instrumental to the growing of my brand today.

From there, I have founded different businesses including HTS Business School and HTS Shuttle Services which is the first intracity transport company in Nigeria
"
                android:textColor="#000000"
                android:textSize="20sp" />
            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginTop="3dp"
                android:text="MY MOTIVATION"
                android:textAlignment="center"
                android:textAllCaps="true"
                android:textColor="#000000"
                android:textSize="30sp"
                android:textStyle="bold" />
            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginTop="3dp"
                android:fontFamily="sans-serif"
                android:paddingLeft="8dp"
                android:paddingRight="8dp"
                android:text="My motivation has always been to help solve the unemployment problems we have in Nigeria. It pains me to see graduates roaming the streets in the name of looking for a job after sending years in the university. Because I believe Nigerian youth have what it takes to build global businesses I seek every opportunity to change the mindset that they are not good enough
HOW I OVERCOMED MY CHALLENGES
Each time I fail I tried to learn from the mistakes.
After school I decided to attend as many seminars as I can, I attended several paid training and I even had to enrol in CVL Mentorship programme of Prof. Pat Utomi and that was one of the turning point for my career. Through these forum and programmes I learnt a lot about how to build structures around my business.
Even when things are not working well I try to stay positive and with persistence I always overcome
 MY ADVICE
Young entrepreneurs often believe that money is everything but I don't think so. I advise them to go for knowledge, I advise the to go for personal development, I advise them to look out for mentors who can help them get better in life. I have started a business worth millions yet my one kobo did not enter into it. I learnt how to leverage, I learnt how to build with other peoples money and I also learnt to build systems, all these are more important than money.
Next advice I have for them is that they should learn not to run away from problems, because problems are opportunities
"
                android:textColor="#000000"
                android:textSize="20sp" />



        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</LinearLayout>